A Guide to the Documents from the County Manager's Library, 1889-1994
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
- County Board
  - Minutes, Agendas (by month)
    - March 1957 (Box 54)
    - April 1957 (Box 54)
    - May 1957 (Box 54)
    - June 1957 (Box 54)
    - December 20, 1975 (Box 54)
  - Papers on Incorporation
    - Charter of the City of Arlington, 1946 (Box 54)
    - Report on Incorporation of Arlington, 1952 (Box 54)
    - Arlington. Citizens Study Commission, establishment of, County Board Resolution, 1952 (Box 54)
  - Reports to the Board
    - Analysis of Tire Operating Conditions, Motor Truck Fleet, Goodyear (3 small photos), 1935 (Box 54)
    - Acquisition of the Moran Tract near Glencarlyn for Park Purposes, 1939 (Box 54)
    - W. V. & M. Coach Co. - Cancellation of Tokens (Brief), 1952 (Box 54)
    - Final Report & Proposed Charter for City of Arlington, Commission on Incorporation, 1959 (Box 54)
    - Urban Renewal, Report, County Manager, 1961 (Box 54)
    - Drug Abuse Problem of Arlington, Appraisal, 1970 (Box 54)
    - Documentation Concerning Allegations by E.R. Bourdon and Responses to Same, County Manager, 1978 (Box 55)
    - Study Commission of the City/County Form of Government (Preliminary), 1979 (Box 55)
  - Reports to Citizens
    - Annual Reports, 1955-56, 1959-60, 1962-63, 1966, 1976, 1983, 1984, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Urban Renewal (proposed Redevelopment & Housing Authority), 1958 (Box 55)
    - Arlington Community Services Board Annual Report, 1985 (Box 55)
  - Other Reports
    - Potomac River Bridges, Report to Board of Commissioners, District of Columbia, 1952 (Box 55)
  - Ordinances
    - Development near Metrorail stations; Pay Television (amendment); Parking Meter Zone Rates, 1980 (Box 55)
  - Directories
    - Telephone, 1972-1973, 1977-1978 (Box 55)
    - Various Community Organizations, 1994 (Box 55)
- Judicial
  - Audit Reports - County Clerk & Clerk of the Circuit Court
    - 1936 (Box 55)
    - 1941 (Box 55)
    - 1942 (Box 55)
    - 1943 (Box 55)
    - 1944 (Box 55)
    - 1945 (January-May) (Box 55)
    - 1945 (May-December) (Box 55)
    - 1946 (Box 55)
    - 1947 (Box 55)
    - 1948 (Box 55)
    - 1949 (Box 55)
    - 1951 (Box 56)
    - 1953 (Box 56)
    - 1955 (Box 56)
    - 1956 (Box 56)
    - 1957 (Box 56)
    - 1958 (Box 56)
    - 1959 (Box 56)
    - 1960 (Box 56)
  - Audit Reports - Juvenile & Domestic Relations Court
    - 1955 (Box 56)
    - 1957 (Box 56)
    - 1958 (Box 56)
    - 1959 (Box 56)
    - 1960 (Box 56)
    - 1962 (Box 56)
    - 1963 (Box 56)
    - 1964 (January - September) (Box 56)
    - 1964 (September - December) (Box 56)
    - 1965 (Box 56)
    - 1966 (Box 56)
    - 1971, 1972 (Box 56)
  - Studies
    - Arlington County Juvenile & Domestic Relations Court, 1973 (Box 56)
    - Arlington County Juvenile & Domestic Relations Court, Response, 1974 (Box 56)
    - History of Arlington County Juvenile & Domestic Relations Court, Caroline J. Brown, 1983 (Box 56)
  - Pamphlets
    - County Court of Arlington County VA, Report, Judge Hugh Reid, 1944-1947 (Box 56)
    - Courtroom Procedure & Your Rights (no date) (Box 56)
  - Telephone Directories, Court House
    - 1966-1967 (Box 56)
- Personnel
  - Pay Recommendations & Data
    - FY 1977 Pay Recommendations to County Board, February 1976 (Box 56)
    - FY 1977 Pay Recommendations to County Board, March 1976 (Box 56)
    - County & Private Industry Pay Data, 1976 (Box 56)
    - County & Federal Pay Charts, 1971-1977 (Box 56)
    - Fire & Police Privates' Pay, Selected Cities, 1975 (Box 56)
    - Employee Salary Lists, 1973, 1976 (Box 56)
    - Tabulation of Classes by Pay Grades, no date (Box 57)
  - Personnel Policy Issues
    - Tenure of County Manager & Appointment of Department Heads, Ballot Question, Arlington Citizens' Study Commission on Local Government, 1952 (Box 57)
    - A Design for a Computerized Payroll & Personnel Records System, Public Administration Service, 1965 (Box 57)
    - Employee & Management Perceptions of Arlington County Personnel System, National Training & Development Service, 1973 (Box 57)
  - Pay Plans
    - 1952 (Box 57)
    - 1958 (Box 57)
    - 1975 (Box 57)
    - 1978 (Box 57)
    - 1980 (Box 57)
  - Position Classification Plans
    - 1947 (Box 57)
    - 1968 (1) (Box 57)
    - 1968 (2) (Box 57)
    - 1968 (3) (Box 57)
  - Information for Employees
    - Personnel Rules, 1935 (Box 57)
    - Personnel Rules, 1956 (Box 57)
    - Employee Handbooks, 1948, 1954, 1959, 1965 (Box 58)
    - Employee Handbooks, 1968, 1971 (Box 58)
- Public Works
  - History, Organization, Regulation
    - Annexation Case, Report, C.L. Kinnier, 1929 (Box 58)
    - "Road & Street Improvements since May 1, 1928," 1930 (Box 58)
    - Sewer Project Statement, County Board, 1933 (Box 58)
    - Public Works Legislation, Report #133, League of Virginia Municipalities, 1933 (Box 58)
    - Rules for Office and Field, Sanitary Division, 1933 (Box 58)
    - "Existing State & Federal Highways & Proposed Additions, 1935-1945," 1935 (Box 58)
    - Water Supply of Arlington County, VA, Thesis, Thomas P. Wharton, 1937 (Box 58)
    - Instructions, Standards, Specifications, County Engineer, 1937-1942 (Box 58)
    - Ordinance, Street & Highway Construction & Development, 1938 (Box 58)
    - Major Thoroughfares & Collector Streets, Plan & Report, 1941 (Box 58)
    - Capital Improvement Program, Department of Public Service, 1946 (Box 58)
    - Sidewalk, Curb & Gutter Construction, Rules & Regulations, 1944 (Box 58)
    - Bond Issues, Proposed, on Five Programs (4 Divisions): Highway, Planning, Public Buildings, Sanitation, 1947 (Box 58)
    - Refuse Incinerating Plant, Official Opening, Program, 1950 (2 copies) (Box 58)
    - Washington Metropolitan Regional Sanitary Board, Organization & Purposes (with clipping, insignia), 1960 (Box 58)
    - Sanitary Sewer System, History, R.M. Wirt & F.H. Doe, 1920-1951 (Box 58)
    - Major Thoroughfare Plan, Office of Planning, 1959 (Box 58)
  - Sanitation Division
    - Storm Water Sewers, Master Plan, Chester Engineers, 1943 (Box 59)
    - Annual Report, Sanitation Division, R.M. Wirt, 1946 (Box 59)
    - Annual Report, Sanitation Division, R.M. Wirt, 1947 (Box 59)
    - Annual Report, Sanitation Division, F.H. Doe, Jr, 1948 (Box 59)
    - Sewage Disposal, Report, Alexander Potter Assoc., 1954 (Box 59)
    - Lower Pimmit Run Watershed, Sewerage Service, Joint Fairfax-Arlington Report, 1955 (Box 59)
    - Sewage Disposal in Northern Virginia, Report, 1955 (Box 59)
    - Sewage System Planning in Arlington County, VA, Alexander Potter Associates, 1956 (Box 59)
    - Arlington County and the Potomac River Pollution Problem, F.H. Doe, Jr, 1957 (Box 59)
    - Arlington's Pollution Abatement Program, Report, F.H. Doe, Jr, 1958 (Box 59)
    - Secondary Treatment Facilities, Scheduling Construction, memo, A.T. Lundberg, 1958 (Box 59)
    - Sewerage System Planning, Annex #1, F.H. Doe, Jr., 1960 (Box 59)
    - Sanitary Sewerage Sys Master Plan, Arlington County Planning Commission, 1961 (Box 59)
    - Sewage Treatment Study, Alexander Potter Assoc., 1963 (Box 59)
    - Secondary Treatment Facilities, differences in cost estimates, memo, Alexander Potter Assoc., 1965 (Box 59)
    - Tertiary Treatment, Progress Report, Alexander Potter Associates, 1970 (Box 60)
    - Sanitary Sewer System Study, Vol 1 - Hayes, Seay, Mattern & Mattern, 1970 (Box 60)
    - Sanitary Sewer Surcharge During Hurricane Agnes, Study - Hayes, Seay, Mattern & Mattern, 1973 (Box 60)
    - Alternatives for Disposal of Biological Sludges, Alexander Potter Associates, 1975 (Box 60)
    - Environmental Assessment, Water Pollution Control Plant, Camp, Dresser & McKee, 1975 (Box 60)
    - Advanced Waste Treatment Facilities, Environmental Assessment (Preliminary), 1975 (Box 60)
    - Advanced Waste Treatment Facilities, Environmental Assessment (Final), 1975 (Box 60)
    - Sanitary Sewerage System Master Plan Summary, Comments, 1972 (Box 60)
    - Energy Recovery Project, Technology Assessment, Sanders & Thomas, Inc., 1983 (Box 60)
    - Energy Recovery Project, Site Analysis, 1983 (Box 60)
    - Energy Recovery Project, Feasibility Analysis, 1983 (Box 60)
    - Sewage Treatment Plant, Annual Report, 1957 (Box 60)
    - Sewage Treatment Plant, Annual Report, 1958 (Box 60)
    - Sewage Treatment Plant, Annual Report, 1959 (Box 61)
    - Sewage Treatment Plant, Annual Report, 1960 (Box 61)
    - Sewage Treatment Plant, Annual Report, 1961 (Box 61)
    - Sewage Treatment Plant, Annual Report, 1962 (Box 61)
    - Sewage Treatment Plant, Annual Report, 1963 (Box 61)
    - Sewage Treatment Plant, Annual Report, 1964 (Box 61)
    - Sewage Treatment Plant, Annual Report, 1965 (Box 61)
    - Water Pollution Control Plant, Annual Report, 1966 (Box 61)
    - Water Pollution Control Plant, Annual Report, 1967 (Box 61)
    - Water Pollution Control Plant, Annual Report, 1968 (Box 61)
    - Water Pollution Control Plant, Annual Report, 1969 (Box 61)
    - Water Pollution Control Plant, Annual Report, 1971 (Box 61)
    - Water Pollution Control Plant, Annual Report, 1972 (Box 61)
    - Water Pollution Control Plant, Annual Report, 1973 (Box 61)
    - Water Pollution Control Plant, Annual Report, 1975 (Box 61)
    - Water Pollution Control Plant, Annual Report, 1976 (Box 61)
    - Water Pollution Control Division, Annual Report, 1981 (Box 61)
    - Water Pollution Control Plant, description (no date) (Box 61)
  - Highway Division
    - Sidewalk, Curb & Gutter Const, Rules and Regs, 1950 (Box 61)
    - Ordinance, Const & Devel, Streets & Highways, 1952 (Box 61)
    - Federally Proposed Parkway on Chesapeake & Ohio Canal, Times Herald reprints, 1952 (Box 61)
    - Shopping & Travel Study, Highway Transport Research Branch, 1952 (Box 61)
    - Proposed Controlled Access Parkway & Expressway Sys, 1955 (Box 61)
    - Highway Department, Programs, 1945-1955, Summary, 1956 (Box 61)
    - Case Study of Arlington County Highway Division, Thesis W. H. Gammon, American University, 1956 (Box 61)
    - Highway Study & Priority Ratings, 1956 (Box 61)
    - Storm Water Sewers, Master Plan, Chester Engineers (with revisions by Highway Division), 1957 (Box 61)
    - Location of Interstate Route 66 within Arlington County, Recommendation, County Board, 1958 (Box 61)
    - Interstate Route 66, Alternate Locations, Joint Report, Planning and Public Service, 1958 (Box 61)
    - Interstate Route #66 Report, Office of Planning & Highway Division, 1958 (Box 61)
    - Highway Study & Priority Ratings, Highway Division, 1960 (Box 62)
    - Time Payments for Sidewalk, Curb & Gutter Through Assessments, Highway Division, 1962 (Box 62)
    - Highway Construction Standards, 1964 (Box 62)
    - Snow Removal System, Rosslyn Area, Wilber Smith & Associates, 1964 (?) (Box 62)
    - Management Study, Highway Division, 1965 (Box 62)
    - Highway & Storm Sewer Construction Standards, Department of Transportation, 1966 (Box 62)
    - Design of I-66 from Washington Blvd to Rosslyn, Report, VA Department of Highways, 1970 (Box 62)
    - Master Plan of Storm Water Sewers, Report, 1971 (Box 62)
    - Master Thoroughfare Plan, 1975 (Box 62)
    - Master Bikeway Plan (with 1975 update), 1974 (Box 62)
    - Stormwater Detention Ordinance: Manual of Operation, 1976 (Box 62)
    - Four Mile Run Watershed Management Progress, Annual Report, 1978 (Box 62)
    - Access to Metrorail Stations in Rosslyn-Ballston Corridor, Planning & Engineering Division, 1979 (Box 62)
    - Street Tree Selection, Handbill, Arbor Day, 1984 (Box 62)
    - Street & Highway Department Annual Report, 1944 (Box 62)
    - Highway Division Annual Report, 1945 (Box 62)
    - Highway Division Annual Report, 1946 (Box 62)
    - Highway Division Annual Report, 1947 (Box 62)
    - Highway Division Annual Report, 1948 (Box 62)
    - Highway Division Annual Report, 1949 (Box 63)
  - Water Division
    - Status of Water Department C.L. Kinnier, 1930 (Box 63)
    - Rules & Regulations, Water Department, 1938 (Box 63)
    - Operation of Arlington County Water Department, Outline, A.T. Lundberg, 1940 (Box 63)
    - Water Distribution Systems, Report, Chester Engineers, 1940 (Box 63)
    - State Water Control Board Hearing, Pollution Control, 1950 (Box 63)
    - Water & Sewer Systems, Statutory Background, 1952 (Box 63)
    - Rules & Regulations, Water Division, 1953 (Box 63)
    - Water Supply & Distribution Systems Improvements, Report, Alexander Potter Associates, 1954 (Box 63)
    - Water Works Improvements, C. L. Kinnier, 1954 (Box 63)
    - Water Supply & Distribution Systems Improvements, Alexander Potter Associates, 1954 (Box 63)
    - Water Systems Facilities Master Plan, Input, County Board, 1956 (Box 63)
    - Facts About the Arlington Water Division, 1959 (Box 63)
    - Distribution Sys Improvements, Evaluation, Alexander Potter Associates, 1959 (Box 63)
    - Water Billing Procedure, Customer Service Operations, 1959 (Box 63)
    - Water Billing, Manuals of Procedure, 1960 (Box 63)
    - Alternative Water System Improvements, Lee-Minor Hills Service Area, CH2M Hill, 1976 (Box 63)
    - Water Storage Facilities Study, Department of Utilities, 1977 (Box 63)
    - Additional Finished Water Storage, Engineering Study & Environmental Impact, Dewberry, Nealton & Davis, 1978 (Box 63)
    - Lee Reservoir Construction Status, H. S. Hulme, Jr, 1979 (Box 63)
    - Water Supply Plan, Proposal to Prepare, Montgomery Engineers of Virginia, 1979 (Box 63)
    - Arlington County Water System Study, Montgomery Engineers of Virginia, 1980 (Box 64)
    - Water Department Annual Report, 1937 (Box 64)
    - Water Department Annual Report, 1938 (Box 64)
    - Water Department Annual Report, 1939 (Box 64)
    - Water Department Annual Report, 1940 (Box 64)
    - Water Department Annual Report, 1941 (Box 64)
    - Water Department Annual Report, 1942 (Box 64)
    - Water Department Annual Report, 1943 (Box 64)
    - Water Department Annual Report, 1944 (Box 64)
    - Water Department Annual Report, 1945 (Box 64)
    - Water Department Annual Report, 1946 (Box 64)
    - Water Department Annual Report, 1947 (Box 64)
    - Water Division Annual Report, 1948 (Box 64)
    - Water Division Annual Report, 1949 (Box 64)
    - Water & Sewer Charges, Info for Domestic Accounts, n.d. (Box 64)
- Citizen Initiatives for County Improvement (CICI)
  - CICI Awards Committee (Correspondence, regulations, project lists etc., scattered)
    - April 1972-June 1973 (Box 64)
    - July 1973-June 1974 (Box 64)
    - July 1974-March 1975 (Box 64)
  - CICI Projects (by sponsor), 1972
    - Animal Welfare League (Box 64)
    - Arlington Chamber of Commerce (Box 64)
    - Arlington County Education Committee (Box 64)
    - Arlington Cubs Boys' Club (Box 64)
    - Arlington Dance Theater (Box 64)
    - Arlington Junior Women's Club (Box 64)
    - Arlington Outdoor Education Association (Box 64)
    - Arlington Parish Council (Box 64)
    - Arlington Retirement Housing Corporation (Box 64)
    - Arlington Soccer Association (Box 64)
    - Ashlawn PTA (playground equip) (Box 64)
    - Ashlawn PTA (Pupil's Choice Program) (Box 64)
    - Black Knights Youth Club (Box 64)
    - Central Arlington Civic Association (Box 64)
    - Common Language (Arlington Bus Project) (Box 65)
    - Courtland Civic Association (Box 65)
    - Glebe School (Box 65)
    - James Madison PTA (Box 65)
    - Key School PTA (Box 65)
    - Leeway Citizens' Association (Box 65)
    - Northern Virginia Mental Health Association (Box 65)
    - Nottingham Elementary PTA (Mini-Park) (Box 65)
    - Nottingham Elementary PTA (Music & art) (Box 65)
    - Planned Parenthood of Northern Virginia (Box 65)
    - Reed Elementary School PTA (Box 65)
    - St Agnes Mothers' Club (Box 65)
    - St Agnes Parent/Teacher Guild (Box 65)
    - St Agnes Social Development Committee (Box 65)
    - Tuckahoe PTA (Civic Info Center) (Box 65)
    - Tuckahoe PTA (Library) (Box 65)
    - Woman's Club of Arlington (Box 65)
  - CICI Projects (by sponsor), 1973
    - Abington PTA (Box 65)
    - Arlington Committee on Optimum Growth (Box 65)
    - Arlington Community Action Program (Box 65)
    - Arlington Historical Society (Improvements 1) (Box 65)
    - Arlington Historical Society (Improvements 2) (Box 65)
    - Arlington Soccer Association (Box 65)
    - Arlington YMCA (Box 65)
    - Arlingtones, The (Box 65)
    - Bellevue Forest Garden Club (Box 65)
    - Clarendon United Methodist Church (Box 65)
    - First Step for Arlington Youth (Box 65)
    - Friends of Thomas Jefferson Jr High Athletics (Box 65)
    - James Madison Elementary School PTA (Box 65)
    - Leeway Citizens' Association (Box 65)
    - Lyon Park Community Center (Box 65)
    - McKinley Elementary School PTA (Box 65)
    - Nottingham Elementary School PTA (Box 65)
    - NW Arlington Lions Club (Box 65)
    - Northern District-Virginia Dietetic Association (Box 65)
    - Oakridge Elementary School PTA (Box 65)
    - Overlee Pre-School Association (Box 65)
    - Planned Parenthood of Northern Virginia (Box 65)
    - Quota Club of Arlington (Box 65)
    - Scott St Children's Community (Box 65)
    - Service League of Northern Virginia (Box 65)
    - St Agnes Parent/Teacher Organization (Box 65)
    - Swanson Jr High School PTSA (Box 65)
    - Taylor School PTA (Save-an-Acre) (Box 65)
    - Taylor School PTA (Soccer goals) (Box 65)
    - Washington Area Bicyclist Association (Box 65)
    - Woman's Auxiliary of Washington Hospital (Box 65)
  - CICI Projects (by sponsor), 1974
    - Abingdon Elementary School PTA (Box 65)
    - Alcoholic Rehabilitation, Inc. (Garden equip) (Box 65)
    - Alcoholic Rehabilitation, Inc. (Veg canning) (Box 65)
    - Alcova Heights Citizen's Association (Box 65)
    - Arlington County Civic Federation (Box 65)
    - Arlington Dance Theater (Box 65)
    - Arlington Historical Society (Box 66)
    - Arlington Soccer Association (Box 66)
    - Arlington WMCA (Exposure '74) (Box 66)
    - Arlington WMCA (Minibikes) (Box 66)
    - Arlington Youth in Ballet (Box 66)
    - Ars Colonia (Box 66)
    - Ashton Heights Civic Association (Box 66)
    - Association for Childhood Education, International (Box 66)
    - Claremont Elementary Student Council Association (Box 66)
    - Connections: New Community Schools, Inc. (Box 66)
    - Ft Meyer Elementary School PTO (Box 66)
    - Glebe School PTA (Box 66)
    - Jackson Elementary School PTA (Box 66)
    - Lions Clubs of Arlington (Box 66)
    - Long Branch PTA Landscape Improvement Committee (Box 66)
    - Martin Luther King Community Center (Box 66)
    - North & South Arlington FISH (Box 66)
    - Northern Virginia Mental Health Association (Box 66)
    - Northwest Arlington Lions Club (Box 66)
    - Patrick Henry PTA (Box 66)
    - Post Cana of Northern Virginia (Box 66)
    - Powhatan Springs Women's Club (Child abuse) (Box 66)
    - Powhatan Springs Women's Club (Spring restoration) (Box 66)
    - Randolph Elementary School PTA (Box 66)
    - Recording Service for Physically Handicapped, Inc. (Box 66)
    - Swanson Jr High School PTSA (Box 66)
    - Taylor Elementary School PTA (Box 66)
    - Taylor Science Club (Box 66)
    - Thomas Jefferson Jr High School (Critter Corner) (Box 66)
    - Thomas Jefferson Jr High School PTA (Broad Run Lab) (Box 66)
    - Wakefield High School PTA (Box 66)
    - Washington Opportunities for Women (Box 66)
    - WNVT/53 (3 productions: County Board Meetings, Performing Arts, History of Arlington) (Box 66)
    - Woodmont PTA (Box 66)
    - Zonta Club of Arlington County (Box 66)
  - CICI Projects (by sponsor), 1975
    - Arlington Dance Theater (Box 66)
- Budget and Finance
  - Audit Reports, County
    - County, FY ended June 30, 1929 (Box 66)
    - County, 1930 (Box 66)
    - County, 1931 (Box 66)
    - County, 1933 (Box 66)
    - County, 1934 (Box 66)
    - County, 1935 (Box 67)
    - County, 1936 (Box 67)
    - County, 1937 (Box 67)
    - County, 1938 (Box 67)
    - County, 1939 (Box 67)
    - County, 1942 (Box 67)
    - County, 1943 (Box 67)
    - County, 1945 (Box 67)
    - County, 1946 (Box 67)
    - County, 1947 (Box 67)
    - County, 1948 (Box 67)
    - County, 1949 (Box 67)
    - County (turnover audit), July 1951-December 1951 (Box 68)
    - County, 1951 (Box 68)
    - County, 1952 (Box 68)
    - County, 1953 (Box 68)
    - County, 1954 (Box 68)
    - County, 1955 (Box 68)
    - County, 1956 (Box 68)
    - County, 1956 (Box 68)
    - County, 1957 (Box 68)
    - County, 1958 (Box 69)
    - County, 1959 (Box 69)
    - County, 1960 (Box 69)
    - County, 1961 (Box 69)
    - County, 1962 (Box 69)
    - County, 1963 (Box 69)
    - County, 1964 (Box 69)
    - County, 1965 (Box 69)
    - County, 1966 (Box 69)
    - County, 1967 (Box 69)
    - County, 1968 (Box 70)
    - County, 1969 (Box 70)
    - County, 1970 (Box 70)
    - County, 1971 (Box 70)
    - County (Treasurer's turnover), December 1971 (Box 70)
    - County, 1972 (Box 70)
    - County, 1974 (Box 71)
    - County, 1975 (Box 71)
    - County, 1976 (Box 71)
    - County, 1977 (Box 71)
    - County, 1978 (Box 71)
  - Audit Reports, County Court
    - Court, December, 1954 (Box 71)
    - Court, Calendar Year 1955 (Box 71)
    - Court, 1956 (Box 71)
    - Court, 1957 (Box 71)
    - Court, 1958 (Box 71)
    - Court, 1959 (Box 71)
    - Court, 1960 (Box 71)
    - Court, 1962 (Box 71)
    - Court, 1963 (Box 71)
    - Court, 1965 & January-May 1966 (Box 71)
    - Court, May-June 1966 (Box 71)
    - Court, June-December 1966 (Box 71)
    - Court, 1967, 1968 (Box 71)
  - Audit Reports, Supplemental Retirement System
    - Retirement, FY ended June 1954 (Box 71)
    - Retirement, 1955 (Box 71)
    - Retirement, 1956 (Box 71)
    - Retirement, 1957 (Box 71)
    - Retirement, 1958 (Box 71)
    - Retirement, 1959 (Box 71)
    - Retirement, 1960 (Box 71)
    - Retirement, 1961 (Box 72)
    - Retirement, 1962 (Box 72)
    - Retirement, 1963 (Box 72)
    - Retirement, 1964 (Box 72)
    - Retirement, 1965 (Box 72)
    - Retirement, 1966 (Box 72)
    - Retirement, 1967 (Box 72)
    - Retirement, 1968 (Box 72)
    - Retirement, 1969 (Box 72)
    - Retirement, 1970 (Box 72)
    - Retirement, 1971 (Box 72)
    - Retirement, 1972 (Box 72)
    - Retirement, 1976 (Box 72)
  - Audit Reports, School Board Supplemental Retirement System
    - School Board, FY ended June 1975 (Box 72)
  - Audit Reports, Sewerage System Bond Funds
    - Sewage System, September 1951-June 1952 (Box 72)
  - Audit Reports, Northern Virginia Cigarette Tax Board
    - Cigarette Tax Board, FY ended June 1971 (Box 72)
  - Audit Report, Flood Damage
    - Flood damage, June 1972-June 1974 (Box 72)
  - Audit Report, Northern Virginia Transporation Commission
    - Transportation, July 1970-January 1974 (Box 72)
  - Audit Report, Comments
    - County, FY ended June 1973, accountants' comments (Box 72)
  - Audit Reports, Federal Revenue Sharing Trust Fund
    - Year ended June 30, 1973 (Box 72)
    - 1974 (Box 72)
    - 1975 (Box 72)
  - Audit Reports, County Board Insurance Fund
    - 1955 (Box 72)
    - 1957 (Box 72)
    - 1958 (Box 72)
  - Budgets, County (listed by fiscal year)
    - Financial Statements, 1930 (Box 72)
    - Approved, Financial Statements, 1931 (Box 72)
    - Approved, Financial Statements, 1932 (Box 72)
    - 1933 (pencil draft) (Box 72)
    - Financial Statements, 1933 (Box 72)
    - Approved, 1933, proposed, 1934 (Box 72)
    - Proposed, 1935 (Box 73)
    - Proposed, 1936 (Box 73)
    - Approved, 1938 (Box 73)
    - Approved, 1939 (Box 73)
    - Approved, 1940 (Box 73)
    - Approved, 1941 (Box 73)
    - Summary, 1942 (Box 73)
    - Proposed, 1942 (Box 73)
    - Summary, 1943 (Box 73)
    - Proposed, 1943 (Box 73)
    - Summary, 1944 (Box 74)
    - Proposed, 1944 (Box 74)
    - Summary, 1945 (Box 74)
    - Proposed, 1945 (Box 74)
    - Proposed, 1946 (Box 74)
    - Proposed, 1947 (Box 74)
    - Proposed, 1948 (Box 74)